criticalmass.com 2008-06-22

# Critical Mass - Website Privacy Policy

This web page describes the privacy policy guidelines regarding the collection and use of personal or corporate information that you provide to CRITICAL MASS INC., its group companies and successors (collectively "CRITICAL MASS� or �we"). Your right to privacy is very important, and our policy is in place to protect your personal information. We recognize that when you choose to provide us with information about yourself, you trust us to act in a responsible manner.

### What personal information do we collect?

We collect only that information that we need in order to maintain a high level of service to you.During your visit to criticalmass.com, we generally will not collect any personally-identifiable information about you, such as your name, address, phone number or e-mail address. We may, however, collect non-personally-identifiable (anonymous) information such as:

  * Your IP address (a unique number assigned to every computer on the Internet) 
  * Your domain type (e.g., .com, .net, .edu) 
  * Standard information included with every communication sent on the Internet, such as browser type, operating system, browser language, service provider and local time

We do gather personally-identifiable information on our CM sites when and where you voluntarily provide it. For example, if you submit your resume, we will ask you to provide things like your name, address, e-mail address, phone number, facsimile number and other information. Should you choose not to provide such information it may hinder our ability to serve your interests.

### How do we protect your privacy?

We will take appropriate steps to protect your privacy and take reasonable security measures to protect your personal information in storage. We do not provide your personal information to other companies without your permission, with the following exceptions:

  * Personally-identifiable information may be processed for us by outside vendors, who are obligated to keep such information confidential 
  * We will provide personally-identifiable data to governmental authorities only as required by law

### What about the use of cookies?

CRITICAL MASS does occasionally use cookies to create a better experience on our sites. A cookie is useful information gathered by your browser and stored on your hard drive, enabling your PC to "remember" some useful items when you return to a web site.

No information which personally identifies you will be collected through the cookies. You can set your browser to notify you before you receive a cookie in order to accept or reject it, or you can set your browser to turn off all cookies. If you choose to disable cookies in your browser, you can still access most of the CM sites.

### How do we use your information?

We may use the information provided by cookies and IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the CM Sites, or for research and marketing purposes to help us refine our marketing approach.

### Links

The CM Sites contain links to other web sites belonging to clients and other sites of interest to our users. CRITICAL MASS does not control the privacy practices of these other sites.

### Questions?

CRITICAL MASS welcomes comments and questions on this policy, sent to the CRITICAL MASS legal department: Attn: General Counsel, 402 - 11 Ave. S.E., Calgary, Alberta, CANADA T2G 0Y4. You may also contact us by e-mail at: [legalmatters@criticalmass.com](mailto:legalmatters@criticalmass.com)

This privacy policy was last updated on November 1, 2006. CRITICAL MASS may modify the provisions of this privacy policy from time to time. The new provisions will be effective as soon as they are posted. Please check this page periodically to ensure that you are aware of any change. These are our current privacy policy guidelines that can be modified at any time by CRITICAL MASS. This is not a contract.
